Do you know
how rapidly medical inflation is rising? About 8%
per year. How many families
go into debt due to paying hospital bills? Approximately
1 million
families. Over the past 9 years, I have provided
health insurance to over 1,000 families
and freed them from the fear of paying hospital bills.
When we
insure ourselves and our loved ones, our
families avoid debt during medical emergencies and can live a
tension-free
life. Today, I want to tell you
what health insurance is and
its benefits. Health
insurance
covers health emergencies in our families. Health
insurance covers expenses like medical bills, hospitalization
costs, consultation fees, and
ambulance charges.
For this, you have to pay a fixed premium at a fixed time.
You can get
health insurance for your family, including your spouse, dependent parents, and children.
With rising inflation, medical expenses are increasing.
This well-designed health insurance
ensures that your hard-earned money is
n't spent on paying hospital bills.
Health insurance allows you to take good care of your family without worrying about money.
Health insurance gives you the freedom to get treatment. It provides you peace of mind and
security. If you get
your treatment done in the company's panel hospital, then the
company provides you cashless facility,
this means that you do
not need to pay anything for the treatment except
those expenses which are not covered by your policy.
Some people think that since we are
young, there is no need to get a policy.
Everyone should understand this that the younger you are when you
take the policy, the lower will be the premium.
Hello, my name is Kalpana Agarwal.
If you want to get your insurance done, then
call on this number and subscribe to this channel.
Thank you.